Contact

7064951212 (Mobile) latrell.wms@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/latrell-williams-05b595a5 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Clinical Research Emergency Room Healthcare

LaTrell Williams

Emergency & Dialysis RN

Augusta, Georgia

Summary

Experienced Emergency Room Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA), Healthcare Information Technology (HIT), Acute Care, and Critical Care Nursing. Strong healthcare services professional with an ADN focused in Registered Nursing, currently pursuing a BSN.

Experience

American Renal Associates Dialysis Nurse September 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months) Augusta, Georgia

Soliant

Travel Registered Nurse September 2017 - September 2018 (1 year 1 month) Tucker, GA

HCA South Atlantic Division 2 years 6 months

Trauma Nurse Lead October 2016 - August 2017 (11 months)

Augusta, Georgia

Emergency Department Staff Nurse March 2015 - August 2017 (2 years 6 months) Augusta, Georgia

TNCC, ENPC, ACLS, PALS, BLS

PruittHealth
Clinical Nurse Liaison
March 2014 - March 2015 (1 year 1 month)

University Health Care System
Emergency Department Staff Nurse
August 2012 - March 2014 (1 year 8 months)

Aiken Regional Medical Centers, Inc. Emergency department staff nurse July 2011 - February 2013 (1 year 8 months) Aiken, South Carolina

Education

South University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2018 - 2020)

Aiken Technical College
Associate of Science (A.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2008 - 2011)